chami.com 2015-02-09

# Privacy Statement

The following statement discloses information gathering and dissemination practices for htmlkit.com, html-kit.com, chami.com and chamisplace.com web sites (referred to as "HTMLKIT.COM").

#### Personal Information

HTMLKIT.COM may request and collect personal information when you request specific information or make a purchase. The requested information is clearly identified on the specific pages. HTMLKIT.COM does not sell such personal information you provide to third parties.

#### Public Forums

HTMLKIT.COM makes forums, message boards, feedback forms, guest books, newsgroups and/or other public forums available to users as part of technical support options and as a way to interact with users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information.

#### Security

HTMLKIT.COM online order forms use the secure socket layer protocol and digital IDs to secure purchasing information transferred between your browser and the HTMLKIT.COM server.

#### External Links

HTMLKIT.COM contains links to other sites that are not under its control. HTMLKIT.COM is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such external Web sites.

#### Cookies

Some pages on HTMLKIT.COM use cookies to remember session state, which is required by online tools such as shopping carts, login managers, etc. You can [disable and/or manage these cookies in your browser](http://www.html-kit.com/e/go.cgi?i=PG_PRIVACY_COOKIES), however some online tools may not function to the fullest extent without cookies.

#### Advertisements

Some HTMLKIT.COM pages display advertisements. Ads that are originating from HTMLKIT.COM servers do not use cookies. Some pages may also display ads originating from third-party servers. These third-party ads may place and read cookies on your browser, or use web beacons to collect information related to serving ads. In other words, some third-party companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. You have the option to [disable and/or manage these and other cookies in your browser](http://www.html-kit.com/e/go.cgi?i=PG_PRIVACY_COOKIES).

#### Automatically Logged Information

HTMLKIT.COM uses standard information such as IP address and browser name automatically logged by web servers to help diagnose problems with the Internet connection, servers and tools that generate browser-specific information; to administer systems and to predict future traffic trends for managing resources such as bandwidth.

#### Contact Information

Please [send any questions](http://www.html-kit.com/cgi-bin/misc/contact.pl?id=103232&t=HTMLKit.com%20Privacy) about this privacy statement, the practices of HTMLKIT.COM sites, or your dealings with these Web sites.
